{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517315021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517315021"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" b3d9aa9c-bca0-4f0f-a577-62c981609e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517327283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517327282"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" b3d9aa9c-bca0-4f0f-a577-62c981609e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517333850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517333848"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" b3d9aa9c-bca0-4f0f-a577-62c981609e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517355916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517355916"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" b3d9aa9c-bca0-4f0f-a577-62c981609e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517369510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517369509"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" b3d9aa9c-bca0-4f0f-a577-62c981609e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517379715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517379715"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517385581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517385581"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517387174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517387174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517389525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517389525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517391095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517391094"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GARI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517393527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517393527"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GARI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517395126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517395126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GIZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517397946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517397946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GIZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517399577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517399576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517401789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517401788"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517403418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517403418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GUNIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517405966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517405966"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GUNIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517407583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517407582"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GAUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517410079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517410079"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GAUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517411633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517411633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GODORO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517414079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517414079"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GODORO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517415700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517415700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517417892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517417891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517419898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517419897"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517419996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517419996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517450880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517450879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 4805329d-b9f8-47bb-931a-29282d3a732c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" GOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517450992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517450992"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 0a9b5ce3-a648-41ec-8e54-12f4cc7a86ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517458454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517458454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 0a9b5ce3-a648-41ec-8e54-12f4cc7a86ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517466890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517466890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 0a9b5ce3-a648-41ec-8e54-12f4cc7a86ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517479026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517479026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" START_KUMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517479929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517479928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517481848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517481848"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517483067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517483067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517483165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517483165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517493176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517493175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_184125"," gameId":" 17f4a958-1cfd-4f31-8983-97e35bc10ea6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}